You two keep an eye on her.
I'll find someone to ask.
Brother Long.
I owe you 45,000, right?
Do I get 5,000 back?
Forget it, keep it.
Are you asking me for money?
Take it.
Leaving the door open in broad daylight isn't a good idea, is it?
Who are you?
Who am I?
Why are you looking at me?
Get him.
He looks like a cop.
I can read.
This watch,
what's going on with it?
Whose is it?
This watch is mine.
Whose is it really?
Mine, Officer.
Yours?
Okay, then come with me.
This watch is linked to a criminal case.
We need to investigate.
Officer,
this watch isn't mine.
Not yours?
It's not mine.
Hers.
Zhao Lu.
I know.
This watch isn't yours either.
Come with us.
Let's have a chat at the station.
Hurry, Lu.
Go with the officer.
Get your shoes.
Just say you don't want the money
anymore.
You people.
Take care, officer.
Tell me, how did you get this watch?
I stole it.
I didn't want to.
But I owe people money.
You saw it today.
Guys like Long.
If you came a step later, I would've...
Besides.
The guest in 208,
he just left the watch on the nightstand.
He didn't keep an eye on it himself.
I just borrowed it for an emergency.
And then?
How did you steal it?
In his room,
isn't there a dumbwaiter?
I slipped it out through the dumbwaiter.
I swear,
it's my first time doing this.
My hands are trembling from fear.
I didn't think the watch was worth much.
Later, I found out it's worth 50,000.
I was thinking that after things quieted down,
I would sell the watch.
I didn't expect
that he would find out.
You can't just kill him to silence him
because he found out you stole it.
What are you talking about, silencing him?
Silence who?
No, I killed someone?
You're acting, right?
What acting?
No, who died?
Li Ting died.
He died in Room 208.
He died?
How could he be dead?
Officers,
if you say I stole, I admit it.
But I wouldn't dare kill anyone.
I try to avoid him as much as possible.
Avoid him?
Why did you want to avoid him?
How could I not?
He bothered me every day.
That day, I was cleaning his room
and ran into him again.
What are you doing?
You again.
Didn't I say I don't need cleaning?
Done.
Are you trying to steal something again?
What kind of person are you?
Don't touch my suitcase.
Okay.
I am warning you for the last time.
Do not touch my things without my permission.
Don't move. Don't move.
Where is my watch?
You won't let this watch thing go, will you?
Didn't you already search me?
I didn't take it.
Still won't admit it, huh?
Do you really think I don't know how you stole my watch?
I know how you took it.
Do you want me to call the police right now?
Don't call the police. Don't.
Please don't call the police.
I took it.
I'll go home and get it for you.
It's fine if you don't want to return it.
How about keeping me company for a night?
Do you think your looks are worth my watch?
Go get the watch.
Take the mop away.
Dumbwaiter.
Is this the reason you quit on May 13th?
Yes.
I couldn't work there anymore.
Couldn't work?
I now have every reason to suspect you.
Because Li Ting said you stole,
you sought personal revenge
and killed him to silence him.
No, officer.
You need evidence to back up your words.
There are security cameras at the door.
How could I have gone in and out?
Didn't you just say there's a dumbwaiter?
A dumbwaiter?
That's for sending food, okay?
Someone my size would get stuck in it.
Have you ever been in it?
How do you know you'd get stuck?
Why don't you try it?
See if you get stuck.
Unless it's a kid.
Ma'am.
The dumbwaiter's capacity is 35 kilograms.
Doesn't that clear Zhao Lu of suspicion?
Did we all get it wrong?
Isn't this just an accident?
He just fell to his death?
No.
Zhuang Lan's and my analysis can't be wrong.
There must have been a second person at the scene.
Cheng Mo is right.
Captain Zhuang.
The autopsy report is out.
At the exact same spot on the back of the victim's head,
there are indeed signs of a second impact.
A second impact?
Yes.
That explains
why the victim's hands
were in such a strange position.
He didn't die immediately after falling.
Instead, someone grabbed his head
and smashed it hard against the edge of the bathtub.
So.
That's why there are such strange handprints.
Then how did that person get in?
The only ways I can think of are the main door
and the dumbwaiter.
But the dumbwaiter can only hold 35 kilograms.
How could a normal person fit in it?
Could it be a minor
or a dwarf?
That's not right either.
There are traces of cleaning in the dumbwaiter.
But I still found
a newly left partial fingerprint.
Judging from the outline,
it belongs to an adult.
Then who could it be?
In Li Ting's social connections,
there is absolutely no one who fits the description.
There is such a person.
This person is someone close to Li Ting.
So when he was in the room,
Li Ting could take a shower without any reservations.
Zhuang Lan and I analyzed the scene.
From the gap left in the curtains,
we suspect Li Ting had been watching this person.
And this person might be the killer we're looking for.
One person is highly suspicious.
Li Ting even went to see her before he died.
That is his wife,
Lu Chen.
Can't the 513 case be closed yet?
Mainly because we haven't figured out
his MO yet.
Let me tell you.
Keeping the Accident Investigation Team running
has put me under a lot of pressure.
Three days.
I'll give you three more days.
I must see the final report.
Okay.
How is Cheng Mo doing?
His ability to handle cases is quite good.
But sometimes he acts like a child.
If you find him troublesome...
No need.
I'm already used to babysitting.
Go ahead.
Ms. Lu, here's the situation.
It has been confirmed that your husband died in an accident.
You still need to sign here.
Alright.
That's all.
The paperwork is done.
Ms. Lu.
My condolences.
Honey.
I'm taking you home now.
Officer Fang, Mr. Cheng.
Thank you for your hard work.
The paperwork is done.
I'll be leaving now.
My condolences.
I really don't understand.
She is clearly a major suspect.
Why did we let her go so easily?
Where is the evidence?
Take a look at this first.
She has an alibi.
It's too deliberate.
The weather wasn't hot,
but she wore so much
and intentionally walked under the only camera in the village.
Yeah.
But you need evidence.
According to Mr. Shao's estimation,
the time of death was 8:00 PM.
She has a solid alibi, okay?
We need evidence.
Sometimes,
taking a step back is the best way forward.